Hi, welcome to session 15,
嗨，欢迎来到第 15 节课，
in this session, we're going to cover different types of electric guitars,
在这节课中，我们将讨论不同类型的电吉他，
we're going to talk about how pickups work, power chords
我们将讨论拾音器的工作方式，强力和弦，
and how to use them,
以及如何使用它们，
this is all about electric guitars and the heart of rock and roll.
所有都是关于电吉他和摇滚乐的核心。
We're going to learn about other styles though too,
我们也将学习其他风格的吉他，
learn about country guitar playing,
了解乡村吉他的演奏，
it about Chicken Pickin
关于 Chicken Pickin ，
and a little bit about R&B stuff,
一些关于 R&B 的东西，
a little about funk guitar playing as well.
以及一些关于 Funk 吉他演奏。
In the guitar tips section,
在吉他技巧部分，
we're going to cover using guitar effects,
我们将讨论使用吉他效果，
distortion, reverb, chorus, delays,
失真，混响，和声，延迟，
a little bit about [amps and amp] modeling,
一些关于功放和功放建模，
we've got a lot to cover,
我们有很多要涵盖的，
so let's get started.
所以我们开始吧。
Okay, the first thing I wanted to talk about is
好的，首先我想谈的是，
a couple of different types of guitars,
几种不同类型的吉他，
that are mainly used in electric work.
主要用于电子工作。
Okay, there's three basic styles,
好的，有三种基本的风格，
a little variations in them,
它们有一些小的变化，
but here are the basic styles,
但这里是基本的风格，
this is a strato, regular Fender Stratocaster,
这是一个 strato ，常规的 Fender Stratocaster ，
different guitar makers make them,
不同的吉他制造商制造它们，
Fender is the one that started it
Fender 是开始制造它的那个，
and its unique body design,
它独特的机身设计，
and it use single coil pickups,
它使用单线圈拾音器，
it's real good for pop things,
这对流行音乐来说很好，
get a little bit of a sweeter sound with a single coil sound,
单线圈声音会有一点甜美的声音，
a little bit of a smaller sound,
声音会有一点小一点，
but very articulate and dynamic,
但非常清晰和动感，
that's a strato.
这是一个 strato 。
Okay, now we've got a telecaster,
好的，现在我们有一个 telecaster ，
this is telecaster,
这是 telecaster ，
is a little bit,
有一点，
notice the body shape is a little bit different,
注意琴体形状有一点不同，
still has the cut away here at the bottom,
底部仍然有缺角，
but the body shape is a little bit different,
但琴体形状有一点不同，
they're generally a little bit heavier than a strato as well,
他们通常也比 strato 重一点，
although it depends on what type of wood is used,
尽管这取决于使用什么类型的木材，
the weight of it,
它的重量，
the thing that affects what your sound is going to be mainly your pickups
影响你的声音的东西主要是你的拾音器，
a little bit of what your strings are,
一些是你的弦是什么，
everything else, what type of wood, this is made out of,
其他所有东西，这是由什么类型的木材制造的，
whether you have gold or silver tuners at the top,
你的顶部是金色或银色调音器，
really doesn't mean anything with how your guitar is going to sound,
与你的吉他的声音没有任何关系，
anyway, this is a good telecaster,
这是一个很好的 telecaster ，
telecasters are used almost exclusively for country guitar playing,
telecaster 几乎都是用来乡村吉他演奏的，
a lot for good Blues,
很多好的 Blues ，
a lot for good rock and roll,
很多好的摇滚乐，
this is a good lead kind of guitar,
这是一种很好的主音吉他，
a little bit on the harsher side of things,
有点刺耳的一面，
can get real warm and fuzzy with them,
可以变得非常温暖和模糊，
but these are just good for good rock and roll stuff,
但这些是好的摇滚的东西。
now let's talk about one more.
现在让我们再说一把。
Okay, the third guitar I want to talk about is 335,
好的，第三把吉他我想说的是 335 ，
Gibson ES-335,
Gibson ES-335 ，
Gibson puts them out,
Gibson 推出了它们，
but Epiphone and many other manufacturers come out with this body style as well,
但是 Epiphone 和许多其他制造商也推出了这种机身风格，
it's a semi hollow body guitar,
这是一把半空的机身的吉他，
what that means is that it does have an opening in the cavity right here,
这意味着它的腔体在这里有一个开口，
so you can hear it a little bit without amplification,
所以你可以在不使用扩音器的情况下听到一点，
let me turn my volume off here,
让我把音量关了，
you can't hear very well,
你听不清楚，
but there is a little bit of sound there,
但有一点声音，
now it uses these big pickups here,
现在它用这些大的拾音器，
these big humbucking pickups,
这些 humbucking 拾音器，
we're going to learn what those are here in a second,
我们稍后会知道这些是什么，
but it's get a real good Jazz, Jazz kind of song,
但它带来很好的爵士乐，
use a lot for Blues playing, BB King uses this,
经常用来演奏 Blues ，BB King 使用这个，
and it really good for Jazz as well,
它也非常适合爵士乐，
you can do a lot of good styles with it,
你可以用它做很多很好的风格，
that's mainly used for Jazz and Blues stuff.
主要用于爵士乐和 Blues 的东西。
Okay, let's talk about different kinds of pickups,
好的，让我们谈谈不同的拾音器，
I chose this guitar,
我选择这把吉他，
because this guitar just happen to have a mishmash of all different kinds of pickups,
因为这把吉他恰好是各种不同拾音器的混合体，
I thought we could get a good example of them.
我想我们可以得到一个很好的例子。
First, let's talk about how pickups work,
首先，让我们来谈谈拾音器是如何工作的，
what are pickups,
什么是拾音器，
well, various styles and shapes on guitars,
好的，吉他上有各种各样的样式和形状，
but here's the three pickups that I have on this telecaster,
但在这个 telecaster 上有三个拾音器，
now I'm going to talk about this one first,
现在我要先谈谈这个，
because it's a little bit easier to see,
因为它更容易看到，
all the pickup is a magnet,
所有的拾音器都是一块磁铁，
it's kind of just a [glorified] magnet,
它是一个[光荣的]磁铁，
you know when you have two magnets and you put them together,
当你有两个磁铁，把它们放在一起时，
you kind of feel that force between them,
你会感觉到它们之间的力量，
that's all this is,
这就是这个，
when I pluck this big metal string,
当我拨动这根大金属弦时，
it is vibrating over the top of that,
它在上面振动，
if you can see that silver circle there,
如果你能看到那里的银色圆圈，
that is actually the tip of a magnet,
那实际上是磁铁的尖端，
okay, so if I play my string,
好的，如果弹奏我的琴弦，
over the top of that string, over the top of that pickup,
在那根弦上面，在拾音器上面，
that magnet, it translates that into electricity,
磁铁就会把它转化为电能，
goes through a little volume, a little bit of tone
通过一点音量，一点音调，
and that's basically your guitar,
这基本上就是你的吉他，
there's not a whole lot of complex electronics on the inside of your guitar,
在你的吉他内部没有很多复杂的电子设备，
it's basically a couple of wires hooked up to these pickups.
它基本上是几根线连接到这些拾音器上。
But there's two different types of pickups, single coil and double coil.
但有两种不同类型的拾音器，单线圈和双线圈。
Now really anything, that's metal vibrating over that pickup will work,
现在，任何东西，是金属在拾音器上振动起作用，
here I have my old tuning fork,
这里我有旧的调音叉，
okay now when I get this going, it's vibrating,
好的，当我让它动起来，它在振动，
and that pickup will sense that vibration as well,
那个拾音器也会感觉到这种振动，
guitar usually have a three way or a five way switch,
吉他通常有三路或五路开关，
if I'm on the way up in front,
如果我把开关放在前面，
it's using the front pickup,
它使用前面的拾音器，
if I'm on the way in the back,
如果我把开关放在后面，
it's listening through this pickup, through the back pickup,
它通过后面的拾音器接收，
I'm in the middle, it's generally using this pickup.
我放在中间，通常使用这个拾音器。
Okay, now regarding pickups,
好的，关于拾音器，
there's really only one type of pickup,
实际上只有一种类型，
it's just basically this magnet,
基本上就是这个磁铁，
now they wind different kinds of winding on it,
他们在上面缠绕不同的线圈，
wind some more, wind some less,
缠绕多点，缠绕少点，
but you'll hear single coil and double coil pickups,
但你会听到单线圈和双线圈的拾音器，
basically all the double coil or humbucking pickup is
基本上所有的双线圈或 humbucking 拾音器都是，
basically two single coils side-by-side or inverted,
单线圈并排或倒置，
you can imagine one is like this and the other one would be down like this.
你可以想象，一个是这样的，另一个向下是这样的。
Okay, now the single coil pickups are great,
好的，现在单线圈拾音器很好，
they just we found out over the years,
他们只是我们多年来发现，
that they're a little bit noisy,
它们有一点噪音，
so when you get two of them,
所以当你有两个时，
that's why they put these humbucking pickups,
这就是为什么他们会放这些 humbucking 拾音器，
they found out if you invert them,
他们发现如果你把它们倒置过来，
then they get a quieter signal,
他们会得到更安静的信号，
so that's the difference between the two,
所以这是两者之间的区别，
they get a slightly difference in sound,
它们在声音上略有不同，
but it's basically the same thing,
但基本上是一样的，
just one of them is two of them and one of them is one of them.
只是其中一个是两个，另一个是一个。
Okay, now let's talk about power chords,
好的，现在我们来谈谈强力和弦，
okay, good all rock and roll stuff involves power chords,
好的，所有的摇滚乐作品都涉及强力和弦，
okay, here's what is involved in a power chord,
好的，这是涉及强力和弦的，
you may hear that term referred to a lot
你可能会听到这个术语被提及很多，
and for a lot of many years,
很多年来，
I didn't know what in the word, they were talking about,
我不知道，他们谈论的是哪个词，
basically it's derived from the major scale,
基本上它是从大调音阶派生出来的，
remember how our major triad was 1 3 and 5,
记得我们的大调三和弦是 1 3 5 ，
on a power chord, we take out the third
在强力和弦上，我们去掉第三个，
and so you're just left with the root and the fifth,
所以你只剩下根音和第五个，
in C, it would be a C and a G
在 C 和弦上，它会是一个 C 和一个 G ，
and I play those at the same time,
我同时演奏这两个，
let me check my distortion there,
让我检查一下我的失真器，
a C and G,
一个 C 和 G ，
if I'm in b flat, it would be a B flat and an F,
如果我是降 B 调的，那就是降 B 和 F ，
the root and the fifth in that particular key,
那个键的根音和五音，
now sometimes you'll even have a chord form,
有时你甚至会有和弦形式，
I'll have the octave down here on this C as well,
我在这个 C 上也有八度，
so you'll see it as a three note chord
所以你会看到它是三个音符的和弦，
or sometimes you'll see it as a two note chord,
或者有时你会看到它是两个音符的和弦，
it's a three note chord, I use all three,
它是三个音符的和弦，我使用所有三个，
it's a two note chord I just used two,
如果是两个音符的和弦，我只是使用两个，
either way is fine,
两种方式都是可以的，
either way or both power chords,
不管是哪种方式，都是强力和弦，
okay, but you're only using two different tones, the root, and the fifth,
但你只使用了两个不同的音调，根音和五音，
okay, most power chords are based off of pivoting off of the fifth string,
好的，大多数强力和弦都是从五弦开始旋转的，
as in this one C B flat
就像这个， C ，降 B ，
or you can also do it off the six string, F and G
或者你也可以从六弦开始， F 和 G ，
and very conveniently, it works out to be the same form.
非常方便，它是相同的形式。
Okay, let's practice jumping through a little bit of that,
好的，让我们练习跳过其中的一小部分，
let's start on the sixth string power chord movable form first,
我们从六弦强力和弦可移动形式开始，
okay, this would be like an F power chord,
这像是 F 强力和弦，
now what do you do with these other three strings,
现在你怎么处理其他三根弦，
well you're not supposed to play them,
你不应该演奏它们，
either kind of mute them down here,
你可以使它们静音，
or you can mute them with this hand as well,
或者你也可以用这只手让它们静音，
using this finger putting it down,
用这根手指把它放下来，
but basically you just try and keep a hand on not going too far down
但你只是让手不要向下太远，
and not playing these extra strings,
不弹奏这些额外的弦，
so this is an F power chord.
所以这是 F 强力和弦。
Okay, now let's jump around a little bit,
好的，现在让我们进一步，
if I wanted it in G,
如果我想要在 G ，
I pivot up to the third fret and play it in G,
我转到第三个调，然后在 G 中弹奏，
if I wanted it in c,
如果我想用 C ，
I have to jump all the way up here to C
我必须一路跳到这里到 C ，
and play it in C,
在 C 中演奏，
see how that works,
看到它是如何工作的，
let's do a couple more,
让我们再做几个，
D,
D ，
let's do A.
让我们来弹奏 A 。
Now, if I want to do it on the fifth string,
现在，如果我想用第五根弦来做，
let's do it on the fifth string,
让我们用第五根弦来做，
this would be like your B power chord version,
这就是 B 强力和弦版本，
okay, same form I got one third and fourth right there,
好的，同样的形式，我得到一 三 五，
let's jump around a little bit,
让我们跳跃一点，
what if I wanted it in E,
如果我想要它在 E ，
I have to jump all the way up here,
我得一路跳到这里，
what about, let's see G, up there,
那么 G 呢，在这里，
what if I want to G on the other string,
如果我想 G 在另一根弦上，
be down there.
在这里。
Okay, now let's do some exercises with them.
好的，现在让我们使用它们做一些练习。
Okay, now that we've practiced jumping in a couple of different places with them,
好的，现在我们已经练习了用它们在几个不同的地方跳跃，
let's do our power chord exercise number one.
让我们来做第一个强力和弦练习。
Okay, starts off on a C chord,
好的，从 C 和弦开始，
sometimes you'll also see it written in notation as a C5,
有时你也会看到它被写成 C5 ，
as opposed to a C7 or Cm or something like that,
不同于 C7 或 Cm 或类似的东西，
you'll see it as a C5,
你会看到它是一个 C5 ，
that's trying to tell you, it's a power chord.
它试图告诉你，这是一个强力和弦。
Okay, so let's look at that first example,
所以让我们看看第一个例子，
I'll do it for one time through nice and slowly.
我会慢慢地做一次。
One, two, ready, go,
一，二，准备，开始，
then I shift on B flat,
然后我换到降调 B ，
then I do F,
然后我换到 F ，
rest,,
停一下，
see how that works,
看到它是如何工作的，
we're just jumping from chord to chord using the same form again,
我们只是用同样的形式从一个和弦跳到另一个和弦，
I'm a guitar player,
我是一个吉他演奏者，
I like the simplest way of doing things,
我喜欢最简单的做事方式，
that's why guitar players love power chords,
这就是为什么吉他演奏者喜欢强力和弦，
we don't have to worry about major minor or anything,
我们不必担心大调，小调或其他什么，
we just have to do,
我们需要做的，
we just have do them on the fifth or the fourth string,
我们四根或五根弦，
fifth of the six string
[六根弦中第五根]，
and do that power chord form.
做强力和弦的形式。
Okay, let's do one more example,
好的，让我们再做一个例子，
before we do that,
在我们做之前，
there are some open power chords,
有一些开放的强力和弦，
I've taught you the movable ones on the fifth string, on the sixth string,
我已经教过你们，第五根弦，第六根弦上的可移动的，
now let's look at an open one,
现在让我们看看开放的，
if I want an E power chord,
如果我想要 E 强力和弦，
it would just be open E,
它应该是开放的 E ，
and it be an E,
它是一个 E ，
which, if you can see,
如果你能看到，
if I moved everything up a half step,
如果我把所有的东西都上移半步，
there would be my F,
那就是我的 F ，
so it's really the same chord,
所以它实际上是相同的和弦，
we just have it in open form,
我们只是有开放的形式，
the other one is an A,
另一个是 A ，
okay, and again I could do all three strings or just two,
好的，再一次，我可以做所有的三根弦，或者只做两根，
whatever I want to do on that,
我想做什么就做什么，
okay, let's look at power chord exercise number three
好的，让我们看一下强力和弦练习 3 ，
and go through that one together.
然后一起来做那个。
Okay, starts on an E,
好的，从 E 开始，
let's play it using our movable chords first
我们先用可移动的和弦演奏它，
and then we'll play it using our open chords.
然后再用开放的和弦演奏。
I'll go nice and slow,
我会慢一点，
one two three four,
一二三四，
rest, rest,
休息，休息，
rest, rest rest,
休息，休息，休息，
one two three,
一二三，
two three,
二三，
to an A.
一个 A 。
Now, let's play some open ones,
现在我们来演奏一些开放的，
here we go,
我们开始，
one two three, two three, or A,
一二三，二三，或者 A ，
okay, now if I sped it up a little bit,
好的，如果我稍微加快一点，
it comes out sounding something like this,
它听起来像这样，
three,
三，
two three four.
二三四。
So you, you just have to keep track of which strings are being muted,
所以你只需要跟踪哪些弦是静音的，
which strings you're picking aggressively down here.
哪些弦你正在积极地拨动。
Okay, now let's learn a little bit about some other styles of electric guitar playing.
好的，现在让我们来学习一些其他风格的电吉他演奏。
Alright, now let's talk about some country styles,
好的，现在让我们来谈谈一些乡村风格，
okay, country, they use a lot of chicken pickin,
好的，乡村，他们使用了很多 chicken pickin ，
it's a funny name,
这是一个有趣的名字，
but basically here's, here's what all that I know about chicken pickin,
但这是我对 chicken pickin 的所有了解，
a lot of times they'll use a thumb pick
很多时候，他们会用拇指拨片，
or they'll have real, they'll grow their nail along, a little bit longer on this hand,
或者他们会在这只手上把指甲长得更长一点，
so I'm using the thumb pick down here
所以我在这里使用拇指拨片，
and then I'm coming up with my first and second finger
然后我会使用我的第一和第二个手指，
or sometimes my third and fourth,
或者有时我的第三个和第四个手指，
so you kind of get this,
所以你可以这样做，
you're playing generally two notes at once
你通常一次演奏两个音符，
or what's called in the [] double staff,
或者所谓的双重东西，
okay, they use a lot of bands and country music,
他们在很多乐队和乡村音乐中使用，
let me play that first lick I was playing again for you,
让我再次为你演奏第一个乐章，
and I'll do it slow it down a little bit.
我会把它放慢一点。
Okay, let's take that apart for a second,
好的，让我们把它分开一秒钟，
let me slow it even further down,
让我再慢一点，
we'll go real slow..
我们会非常慢的。
Okay, there's a whole bunch of combinations of techniques,
好的，有一大堆技术的组合，
we've got some harmonized going in there,
我们有一些和声在这里，
we've got these two fingers plucking up with that,
我们有这两个手指用来拨动，
that's all part of that chicken pickin style,
这是 chicken pickin 风格的一部分，
one of the best chicken pickin guys around,
最好的 chicken pickin 的人之一，
with country guitar playing
在乡村吉他演奏中，
is a wonderful guitarist, by the name of Brent Mason,
是一个很棒的吉他手，名叫 Brent Mason ，
okay, he's playing on just about every country songs you hear on the radio these days,
好的，他唱着你最近在收音机里听到的几乎每一首乡村歌曲，
doing that chicken pickin thing,
做这个 chicken pickin 东西，
and there's all kinds of great [] that you can use for that,
你可以用各种很棒的[]，
that's just an example of one of them,
这只是其中的一个例子，
they also use a lot of bends,
他们也用了很多 bends ，
let's see if I could do a bend to,
让我们看看我是否可以 bend ，
something like that,
像这样的东西，
or maybe I put them together,
或者我把它们放在一起，
they also use arpeggios,
他们也用琶音，
that use a lot of open strings,
用了很多开放的弦，
I'm going to show you one
我会给你们看一个，
and I'll play it real slow for you.
我会慢慢地为你们演奏。
Let's see if I can play a little bit faster.
让我们来看看我能不能弹得更快一点。
As you as you learn these,
随着你学习，
it takes a little bit of time to figure out these open strings,
弄清楚这些开放的弦需要一点时间，
but it's well worth it to get a few of these [] underneath your belt in your tool bag,
但在你的工具包里放几个这些[]是值得的，
so when somebody says,
所以当有人说，
hey, can you play something country,
你能演奏一些乡村音乐，
I don't know anything country,
我不知道任何乡村的东西，
but I can do this,
但我能做这个，
oh, we're in D,
哦，我们在 D ，
I need to do in D, no problem,
我需要在 D 中做，没有问题，
country guitar playing is almost always done,
乡村吉他演奏几乎总是完成，
good guitar keys which is A D and E.
好的吉他调是 A D 和 E 。
Good, now I want to talk about one more style of guitar playing,
好的，现在我想再谈一种吉他演奏风格，
a little bit about Rhythm and Blues, about R&B, funk guitar playing,
关于节奏布鲁斯，关于 R&B ， funk 吉他演奏，
we talked about this a little bit,
我们谈到了一点，
when we're talking about muted picking,
当我们讨论静音拾音时，
but let me emphasize a couple of different things for you.
但让我为你们强调几个不同的东西。
It's a real percussive style,
这是一种真正的击球风格，
so you want to make sure you have a nice good thick pick
所以你要确保你有一个很好的拨片，
and as I'm playing,
像我演奏的，
let me kind of switch pickups here,
让我把拾音器切换到这里，
because I just play this A,
因为我只是演奏 A ，
if I play hard enough,
如果我演奏足够用力，
I kind of get this popping sound,
我会得到这种爆裂的声音，
so I'm just playing.
所以我只是在演奏。
Okay, a little bit about Rhythm and Blues playing,
好的，一点关于节奏布鲁斯的演奏，
they use a lot of that,
他们用了很多这个，
instead of playing a full chord,
不是演奏完整的和弦，
they'll just use a little bit part of a chord,
他们只使用了和弦的一部分，
let only play one more example for you,
让我们再演奏一个这样的例子，
something like that,
像这样的东西，
they use a lot of [] muting,
他们使用了大量的[]静音，
a lot of taking the quarter part, we talked about earlier
大量使用了四分之一部分，我们前面谈到的，
and they used sliding of fourths and fifths,
他们使用了四弦和五弦的滑动，
which, if I'm in A, I just slide up,
如果我在 A ，我就会滑下去，
kind of do it on the root,
在根音上做，
then I do on the fifth,
然后在五音上做，
they use that style a lot.
他们大量使用了这种风格。
Okay, now let's talk a little bit about guitar effects,
好的，现在让我们来谈谈吉他效果，
electric guitar players use them all the time,
电吉他演奏者一直使用的，
there's basically some basic common ones,
有一些基本的共同之处，
that are similar between all different effect boards,
在所有不同的效果板之间是相似的，
that you need to have in your [] to be able to get.
你需要在你的[]中有能够得到的效果。
Okay, first thing I want to talk about is distortions,
好的，首先我想说的是失真，
okay, I've got several different distortions here on my pedal board,
好的，我的踏板上有几个不同的失真，
[] if I [], this is kind of break up the sound a little bit,
如果我[]，这有点打破声音，
some of them have different characteristics.
其中一些有不同的特性。
We switch over this one here,
我们在这里切换到这个，
that wants a little more softer and mellower,
它想要更柔和一点，
use them differently in different situations,
在不同的情况下使用它们的不同，
let me talk to you about one specific type of pedal
让我和你们谈谈一种特定类型的踏板，
and Ibanez Tube Screamer,
Ibanez Tube Screamer ，
okay, this has been around for years
好的，这个已经存在很多年了，
and probably will continue to be around for years and years and years,
可能会继续存在很多年，
now you'll notice distortion pedals have several things in common,
现在你会注意到失真踏板有几个共同点，
they have a drive,
它们有一个驱动，
and they also have a level knob
它们也有一个水平旋钮，
or sometimes you'll say it as gain,
或者有时你会说它是增益（旋钮），
think of it this way,
这样想它，
think of it like a water hose,
把它想象成水管，
okay, the drive is what's your initial what's coming into the system,
好的，驱动是你最初进入系统的东西，
and you can really boost that water hose,
你可以加大水管的音量，
okay, the one the level or the volume on is how much you're actually letting out of that big signal,
水平或音量是指你实际上释放了多少大信号，
so I can control whether I'm having a little signal coming into the system
所以我可以控制是有一个小信号进入系统，
or a huge signal coming into the system,
还是有一个巨大的信号进入系统，
but nothing comes out until I open the spigot on this end and let out whatever,
但在我打开这一端的水龙头并释放任何东西之前，什么都不会出来，
so if I have this huge signal coming here,
所以如果我有一个巨大的信号来到这里，
then I gotta make sure I have my volume down appropriately
我必须确保我的音量适当地降低，
are going to get this massive signal coming out,
才能得到这个巨大的信号，
so if I want to be really distorted,
所以如果我想失真，
I crank this gain all the way up,
我把这个增益一直向上，
get really distorted, really where it's really breaking up,
获得失真，在它真正破裂的地方，
but I only want to allow a little bit of it out
但我只想让它出来一小部分，
or I'm going to have this too much of a massive signal,
否则我会有太多的巨大信号，
it would be too loud,
那就太吵了，
if I just want a little bit of distortion,
如果我只是想要一点失真，
or maybe I don't want distortion at all,
或者我根本不想要失真，
crank this down nice and low
把这个旋转调低一点，
and open this one up nice and big,
把这个打开大一些，
that's relationship between gain and volume.
这是增益和音量之间的关系。
Another pedal that is real common have is a chorus pedal,
另一个很常见的是合唱踏板，
what it's doing,
它是做什么的，
let me see if I can get a good chorus sound
让我看看我能不能得到好的合唱音质，
here's my guitar normal,
这是我正常的吉他，
if I had chorus,
如果我有和音，
chorus expand your sound a little bit,
和音将你的声音扩大了一点，
now there's choruses and flangers and phase shifters,
现在和音， flanger 和移相器，
they're all the same sort of thing,
它们都是一样的东西，
it's taking your sound
它把你的声音，
and taking a little bit sharp, a little bit flat
变得有点尖锐，把它变得平坦，
and making it into a pleasant,
让它变得悦耳，
you can control how much it's diverting the sound or not.
你可以控制它对声音的分流程度。
Next thing everybody needs to have some sort of a delay,
接下来，每个人都需要有某种形式的延迟，
Okay, I'm using a regular Boss digital delay,
好的，我使用的是常规的 Boss 数字延迟，
here there's more exciting ones than this,
这里有比这更令人兴奋的延迟，
but basically they all kind of do the same thing,
但基本上它们都做相同的事情，
I play my note,
我演奏我的音符，
and it fought trails off,
它[击退]了踪迹，
I can control how much it's feeding back,
我可以控制它反馈多少，
how loud that needs to be,
需要多大的声音，
I can make it feedback forever,
我能让它永远反馈，
if I wanted.
如果我想的话。
And also when you do something like that,
而且，当你做这样的事情时，
you can get kind of neat effects.
你可以得到某种整洁的效果。
Okay, so that's a little bit about reverb delays,
好的，这是关于混响延迟的一点，
okay, reverb is more like an echo,
好的，混响更像是回声，
like you would hear in a room,
就像你在房间里听到的，
[] my reverb up,
打开我的混响，
kind of makes it sound like you're in a big place.
听起来像是你在一个很大的地方。
One talk about one more,
谈论另一个，
now I'm gonna use my waffle a little bit,
现在我要用 waffle ，
okay, okay, let's see what can I do,
好的，让我们看看我能做什么，
a little bit about using your wah,
关于使用你的 wah ，
takes a while to get used to the feel of how that cycles through,
需要一段时间来习惯它是如何循环的感觉，
but it's a great effect,
但它是一个很好的效果，
especially in a funk playing,
特别是在 funk 演奏中，
you can get a lot of good use out of wah, okay.
你可以从 wah 中得到很多好的使用。
Now, let's go to our how music works section.
现在，让我们转到我们的音乐工作原理部分。
Okay, very quickly,
好的，很快，
I wanted to touch on a very important concept called the harmonized major scale,
我想讨论一个非常重要的概念，和声大调音阶，
not so important about the name,
名字并不那么重要，
but I want you understand the concept of what's going on,
但我想让你们理解，发生了什么，
if I take a major scale,
如果我用一个大调音阶，
let's say a C major scale,
比如说一个 C 大调，
and I'm going to build things,
我将构建一些东西，
I'm going to stack two-thirds above it,
我将在它上面叠加三分之二，
so I actually have a major triad a one three and five,
所以我有一个大三和弦，一，三和五，
then I stack thirds on all of those going all the way up the scale,
然后我把三分之一叠加在所有那些向上的音阶上，
well the first step, if I do it in C,
第一步，如果使用 C ，
it would be one three and five or C E and G,
它将是一，三，五，或者 C ， E ， G ，
which comes out to be a C major traid.
这是一个 C 大三和弦。
And the next one I would be two four and six,
下一个是二，四，六，
which would be D F and A,
也就是 D ， F 和 A ，
well now if you notice,
如果你注意到，
if you just look at that D F and A
如果你查看看那个 D F A ，
and think of it in the key of D just for a second,
用 D 调考虑一下，
it doesn't turn out to be major turn out to be minor,
它不是大调，而是小调，
a one flat three and five,
一，降三，五，
if I'm looking at in the key of D,
如果我看的是 D 调，
it's very important,
这是非常重要的，
the second step will get you a minor triad.
第二步会得到一个小调的三和弦。
If I go to the next one,
如果我到下一个，
I get E G and B,
我得到的是 E G B ，
okay, that also ends up being a minor triad.
好的，这也是一个小三和弦。
The fourth, F A and C is back to major.
第四个， F A C 回到了大调，
Fifth, back to major, G B and D.
第五个，回到了大调， G B 和 D 。
Sixth, back to minor, A C and E.
第六个，回到小调， A C 和 E 。
Seventh, B D and F, actually ends up being a diminished triad,
第七个， B D 和 F 实际上是一个减弱的三和弦，
if you look at it based off of that B.
如果你基于 B 调来看它。
This becomes real important,
这就变得很重要了，
some of them are major, some of them are minor,
有些是大调，有些是小调，
in any key, any major key it's [] that same relationship,
任何大调都是同样的关系，
which ones are major, the one chord, the four chord and the five chord,
那个是大调，一和弦，四和弦，五和弦，
which ones are minor, the two chord, the three chord, the six chord
哪个是小调，二和弦，三和弦，六和弦，
and one that's off is the seventh, that's diminished,
一个七和弦，是减弱的，
that's a harmonized major scale concept,
这是一个和音大调音阶的概念，
very important,
非常重要，
I would practice that in different keys,
我会用不同的调练习，
you can get an idea of how that flows,
你可以得到一个想法，那是如何流动的，
one four and five major,
一，四，五，大调，
two three and six are minor.
二，三，六，小调。
Okay, let's talk about your assignment for this week,
好的，让我们谈谈你本周的作业，
I would like you to practice the power chords using good technique,
我想让你用好的技巧练习强力和弦，
play the exercises and the song examples in your book,
演奏你书中的练习和歌曲例子，
work out the chicken pickin exercises, that are in there as well
也练习里面的 chicken pickin 练习，
and make some up on your own,
然后自己补一些，
I would like you to practice the sliding fourth and fifth in various key combinations,
我希望你在各种调组合中练习滑行第四和第五键，
those exercise in your book as well,
这些练习也在你的书中，
and don't forget the Jam Along CDs,
不要忘记 Jam Along CD ，
give you plenty of opportunity to get some good practice
给了你很多机会做好的练习，
in power chords, sliding as well as the chicken pickin stuff.
在强力和弦，滑行和 chicken pickin 的东西上。
Okay, we'll see at the workshop.
好的，我们在 workshop 上见。
Okay, now it's our workshop time,
好的，现在是我们的 workshop 时间，
is the time where we work those concepts out that we've learned in session 15,
在这里我们要解决我们在第 15 节课中学到的概念，
get them underneath our fingers.
让它们掌握在我们的手指之下。
Okay, let's review power chords,
好的，让我们复习一下强力和弦，
remember we did them on the fifth string and the sixth string,
记得我们在第五和第六弦上做了它们，
the fifth string version, if I wanted to do a B power chord,
第五弦版本，如果我想做一个 B 强力和弦，
you have your first finger, second fret,
你的第一根手指在第二个品格，
third finger on the fourth fret,
第三根手指放在第四个品格，
pinky covering the third string, fourth fret,
小指在第三根弦第四品格，
okay, get a little [] sound here,
好的，发出一点[]声音，
on the sixth string barre chord, like an F barre chord,
在六弦上，像 F 横按，
not barre chord, what am I talking about power chord, okay.
不是横按，我说的是强力和弦。
So let's jump around in some different places on those,
所以让我们跳到一些不同的地方，
let's say I wanted a G power chord,
假设我想要一个 G 强力和弦，
well, if I did it on the sixth string, it'd be like this,
如果我在六弦上做，它是这样的，
what about if you did it on the fifth string,
如果你在五弦做呢，
what about a C power chord,
那么一个 C 强力和弦呢，
on both the sixth and fifth string,
在六弦和五弦上，
sixth first, C,
首先是六弦， C ，
fifth string.
五弦。
What about E flat,
那么降调 E 呢，
let's do E flat on both strings,
让我们在两根弦上做降调 E ，
six strings to be way up here,
六弦在这里，
fifth string.
五弦。
Make crank on some distortion here
在这里加一些失真，
switch to my [back],
转回来，
pick up get a little more of a rock and roll sound,
来一点摇滚乐的声音，
let's do two more,
让我们再做两个，
lets do a F,
让我们做一个 F ，
six string,
六弦，
fifth string.
五弦。
would you like a B flat,
你想要一个降 B 吗，
six string,
六弦，
fifth string.
五弦。
Power chord exercise number one, do it real slowly.
强力和弦第一个练习，动作非常慢。
One, two ready go,
一，二，准备，开始，
rest rest,
休息，休息，
up be here,
在这里，
back again again.
再来一次。
Good, now let's go power chord exercise number two,
好的，现在我们来做强力和弦练习二，
we'll start this one pretty slow.
我们将非常缓慢地开始。
One, two ready go.
一，二，准备，开始。
Let's skip down to power chord exercise number four,
让我们跳到强力和弦练习四，
we'll take it pretty slow,
我们要慢慢来，
one two three four.
一二三四。
One more time go.
再来一次。
Good, now let's talk about our chicken pickin exercise,
好的，现在让我们来谈谈我们的 chicken pickin 练习，
remember the [] that we learned,
记的我们所学的[]，
let's do it nice and slow.
让我们慢慢来。
One two, ready, go.
一，二，准备，开始。
Slow it down a bit more.
再慢一点。
Now, if I wanted to do that E,
现在，如果我想做 E ，
I moved the whole picture down here
我把整张图片移到了这里，
and it's pretty much the same finger, finger pattern,
它几乎是一样的手指样式，
in E, ready, go.
在 E 中，准备，开始。
Now I can also do it in D,
现在我也可以在 D 中做，
let me just show that to you real quick,
让我快速地向你们展示，
I just have to adjust my fingers instead of being flat here on this,
我只需要调整我的手指，而不是平放在这里，
partial barre with your first finger,
用你的食指部分横按，
I'm gonna use one and two indeed would be,
我要用一弦和二弦，
have a little bit different fingering, a little bit of a finger twister there.
会有一点不同的指法，有点扭曲手指的感觉。
Okay, last one I want to show you is
好的，最后一个，我想给你们看的是，
our descending arpeggio in A using open strings.
我们使用开放和弦下降的琶音。
Okay, we'll go through real slowly,
好的，我们会慢慢来，
cause it's kind of tricky.
因为这有点棘手。
Starts on the A, at the fifth fret,
从第五个品格的 A 开始，
G, then open E string.
G ，然后是开放 E 弦。
Okay, try it again.
好的，再试一次。
One more time, that's just the first half on.
再一次，这只是上半部分。
Okay, okay, so the two parts of that [],
好的，[]的两部分，
we have the first part, the second part,
我们有第一部分，第二部分，
I'll put both together now.
我现在把它们放在一起。
Okay, a little bit faster.
好的，再快一点。
Great, now work on those sliding fourth and fifth exercise as well.
很好，现在还可以做第四和第五滑行练习。
These are some of the colors that you can use in your electric guitar playing,
这些是你可以在电吉他演奏中使用的一些颜色，
that make your playing stand out and be unique,
它们会让你的演奏脱颖而出，变得独特，
so I appreciate you taking the time to listen and to learn,
所以我很感谢你花时间听和学习，
now you, now it's your turn to go and work on it
现在轮到你去努力了，
and become a guitar player that you need to be,
成为你需要成为的吉他手，
I'll catch you later.
我待会再见。